[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
Now we've seen classification in a wide variety of settings and how we can really
我们已经看到了若干不同情况下的分类问题
use to predict a class like a positive or negative sentiment from data.
以及我们怎么从数据中预测 一个句子情绪是正面还是负面
In the regression section, Amy talked about this block diagram that
在回归模型中 Amy用这个模块图
really describes how a machine learning algorithm iterates through its data.
来描述一个机器学习模型怎样一次次 从它的数据中演变
So now let’s take this same block diagram and work through it and
这里我们就还是用类似一个模块图来看看
describe how it works out in the case of classification with sentiment analysis.
它在句子情绪分析这个分类问题中是怎么工作的
So how does it look for classification for
在这个例子中
sentiment, so in this case,
模型是怎么进行情绪分类的呢
the data is the text of the reviews, so
这个例子里 学习数据是 评论的内容
for each review, the text of review is
对每一条评论来说 它的内容
associated with a particular labeled sentiment
都和一个特定的情绪标签联系在一起
From that text of the review, we feed it to through a feature
对那条评论内容来说 我们对它进行一次 特征提取
extraction phase which gives us x, the inputs to our algorithm.
从特征提取中我们得到了我们算法的输入x
And this x here is going to be the word counts.
这里x会是单词计数
So word counts for every data point, for every review.
因此每一条评论我们都可以得到一个单词计数
Now our Machine Learning model is going to take that input data.
接下来我们的机器学习模型会接受那个输入
And so the word counts, as well as some several parameters
也就是单词计数 还有若干其它参数
which I'm calling here w-hat, which are the weights for each word.
这些参数我称之为 w帽 也就是每个单词的权重
Each word.
每 个 单 词
And from, combining these two, we're gonna output the predictions.
然后从单词计数和权重参数中 我们可以计算输出分类器的预测结果
So if the score is greater than zero, it's gonna be positive.
如果结果大于零 我们说结果是正面情绪
If the score is less than zero, it's gonna be negative.
如果小于零我们说是负面情绪
So this output here is the predicted sentiment.
也就是说这里的输出是预测的情绪
And if we're just using the model, we would be done here.
如果我们就打算用这个模型预测结果 我们已经完成任务了
But really, in the machine learning algorithm phase, we're gonna evaluate that
但实际上 在机器学习算法阶段 我们会评估预测结果
result and then feed it back into the algorithm to improve the parameters.
并把评估反馈给模型 从而让模型改进参数
So we're gonna take the predicted sentiment, y-hat and
所以我们会把预测出来的情绪标签  y帽
compare it with the true label for the sentiment.
拿来和真.标签比较
So the sentiment label for each data point.
真.标签也就是每个数据点(每个句子)的真正情绪标签
So that's gonna fit in and
那个比较会反馈回给模型
our quality measure here is gonna be classification accuracy.
我们这里用分类准确率来测量模型质量
Classification accuracy.
分 类 准 确 率
And the machine learning algorithm, which we're gonna discuss in more detail
机器学习算法会尽量提高这个准确率
in the classification course, is gonna take that accuracy and try to improve it.
这一点我们在接下来的分类课程里还会进一步仔细讨论
And the way the improvement works, is by updating the parameter w-hat.
怎么提高准确率呢 就是要更新权重w帽
And that's what the cycle for
这就是这个循环的意思
machine learning algorithm classification would look like.
这个机器学习分类算法的循环
In this module, we've seen how to do classification.
在这一节里 我们学习了怎么做分类问题
We've looked at various examples of where it can be applied.
我们看了好几个分类问题的例子 以及这些例子在什么地方可以得到应用
We'll talked about a few models for building classifications,
我们讨论了构建分类的若干模型
especially in the context of sentiment analysis, we saw some live demos.
特别是针对情绪分析问题 我们看了一些实时演示
And we even built a notebook where we built a classifier from data and
我们甚至构建了一个笔记本 关于我们怎么从数据中构建一个分类器
analyzed it.
并且怎么分析这个分类器
And with this knowledge, you're ready to build an intelligent application
拥有这些知识之后 你就做好了准备
that uses a classifier at its core.
可以构造一个核心是分类器的智慧应用了
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community